# Shreyansh Malewar

Pune (M.H) – 8226071537 – Shreyanshmalewar@gmail.com

#### **About**

A beginner developer with an experience of working in an organization with diverse people and being a part of team where I contributed to make a live project and made sure that I fulfill the role of a group member and meet customer needs, I am looking forward to work within your company.

#### Technical skills

Web Technologies - Developing and Designing Web Pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap. Hands on jQuery, XML, Angular and ReactJS.

Programming Languages – C, Core Java Programming on Servers, J2EE with servlet, JSP(adv java) Framework - Hibernate, Spring, Spring – MVC Boot & REST

Database Technologies - Oracle-SQL, PL-SQL, MySQL, NO-SQL

## Soft - Skills

Confident, articulate, and professional speaking abilities.

Empathic listener and persuasive speaker.

Combine patience, determination, and persistence to troubleshoot organizational demands and client issues.

## **Education**

# **Bachelor Of Technology in Computer Science**

2018 - 2022

Amity University Raipur Chhattisgarh - Aggregate CGPA – 8

## Experience

## **Leap Academy**

10 May 2021 – 28 August 2021

Prodevans Technologies & Red Hat academy, Bengaluru, Karnataka

As a Student Intern I learned basics to intermediate of Red Hat, python with GUI, OOP, also covered basics to intermediate of AWS (amazon web services) & made a live project.

## **Edgate Technologies**

20 May 2020 - 28 June 2020

Texas Instruments, Bangalore, Karnataka

A complete walk through of Advanced Embedded System Design using Tiva C series Microcontroller also learned to design an android application for an embedded or IOT system is what I learned as a *Student Intern*.

## **Certificates**

## Seed InfoTech

August 2022 – July 2023

Full Stack Developer Course - Java

I Learned Web Technologies like HTML5/CSS, Angular, React JS

Prog.Lang. – C, Java, Java core with Frameworks and Database Technologies.

# Additional Information

Consequently 2-year intercollege football championship winner.

Intermediate mountain and road Cyclist for 5 years.

#### Languages

Proficient in Speaking - English, Marathi, Hindi.